Byron Tunnell Papers, Inclusive: 1925-1999, undated, Bulk: 1961-1999
Baylor University, Baylor Collections of Political Materials
- Press, 1953-1994, undated; 10
  - Newsletters, 1993-1994; 2
    - Texas Civil Justice League Advocate, 1993 April (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Texas Business News, 1993 April 12 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Texas Energy Week, 1993 June 7 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Legislative Digest, 1993 June 8 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Bullock ’94, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Speeches, 1961-1999, undated; 11
  Series 11. Speeches, dated 1961-1999, was organized and indexed by Byron Tunnell. Contents include legislative addresses, speeches given to the Jaycees and other civic organizations, and several regarding the oil and gas industry. Others include workshop speeches, retirement affairs, and eulogies. The final speech is the eulogy Tunnell prepared for his long-time friend, Bob Bullock. The series is in chronological order and is in good condition.
  - General, undated (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Handwritten Drafts, undated (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Speech File Index, undated (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Impact of Governmental Regulations, undated (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Criminal Procedure, No. 1, 1961 (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Texas League of Municipalities, 1962 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - The Outlook for 1963, No. 2 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Association of General Contracts, No. 3, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Jaycee Bosses Night, No. 4, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Lawyers in Legislature, Baylor Legal Group, No. 5, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Address to 58th Legislature, No. 6, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Texas National Guard Officer Candidates, No. 7, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Sheriff’s Association, No. 8, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - East Texas Peace Officers Association, No. 9, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Texas Research League, No. 10, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Texas Research League, No. 10-A, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Constitutional Amendments, No. 11, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Civil War Centennial, No. 12, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - President Kennedy Assassination, No. 13, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Sul Ross College, No. 14, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Car/Truck Renting/Leasing Association, No. 15, 1963 (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Kiwanis Club, No. 16, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Jaycees Outstanding Young Men, No. 17, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - Jaycee Bosses Night, No. 18, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - Cranbrook Club, No. 19, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 37)
  - State Government and Constitutional Philosophy, No. 20, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 38)
  - Houston Construction Day, No. 21, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 39)
  - Good Roads Association, No. 22, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Industrial Week, No. 23, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 41)
  - Jaycee Annual Budget, No. 24, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 42)
  - Loyalty Day, No. 25, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Boys State, No. 26, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 44)
  - Power Plant Dedication, No. 27, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 45)
  - East Texas Peace Officers Association, No. 28, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 46)
  - July Fourth Speech, No. 29, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 47)
  - Youth Center Groundbreaking, No. 30, 1964 (Box 22, Folder 48)
  - Attorney General’s Youth Conference, No. 31, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - American Psychiatric Association, No. 32, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Highway Week, No. 33, 1964 October 4 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Texas Municipal League, No. 34, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Rosenberg Address, No. 35, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Shrimp Association of the Americas, No. 36, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - United Daughters of the Confederacy, No. 37, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Texas State Hospitals and Special Schools, No. 38, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Texas Forestry Association, No. 39, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Texas Elementary Principals and Supervisors, No. 40, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 10)
  - Classroom Teachers Association, No. 41, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Valley Bankers Group, No. 42, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Texas State Teachers Association, No. 43, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Texas Woman’s University, No. 44, 1964 November 24 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - South Side Lions Club, No. 45, 1964 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Texas Medical Association, No. 46, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Texas Medical Assistants Society, No. 47, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - American Society for Public Administration, No. 48, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Bosses Night, Jaycees, No. 49, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - Traffic Club of Galveston, No. 50, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Bosses Night, Past Presidents Banquet, No. 51, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Natural Gas Men’s Association, No. 52, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Press Association, No. 53, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  - Joint Session of 59th Legislature, No. 54, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 24)
  - Jaycees Installation Banquet, No. 55, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 25)
  - Landmen’s Association, No. 56, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 26)
  - Jaycees Service Award, No. 57, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 27)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 58, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 28)
  - Texas Oil Jobbers Association, No. 59, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 29)
  - Speaker’s Day, 59th Session, No. 60, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 30)
  - East Texas State Bar of Texas, No. 61, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 31)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers, No. 62, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 32)
  - East Texas Association of Petroleum Landmen, No. 63, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 33)
  - Billion Barrel Celebration, No. 64, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 34)
  - Panhandle Producers and Royalty Owners, No. 65, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 35)
  - Texas Motor Transportation Association, No. 66, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 36)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers, No. 67, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 37)
  - Jaycees Bosses Night Banquet, No. 68, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 38)
  - Petroleum Landmen Seminar, No. 69, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Petroleum Engineers Club, No. 70, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 40)
  - Texas Butane Dealers, No. 71, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 41)
  - Texas Mid-Continent Oil and Gas Association, No. 72, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 42)
  - Natural Gas Processors Association, No. 73, 1965 (Box 23, Folder 43)
  - Permian Basin Petroleum Association, No. 74, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - National Association of Accountants, No. 75, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 76, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Petroleum Landmen and Geological Society, No. 77, 1965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Petroleum Chemical Comm. of West Texas, No. 78, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Texas Manufactures Association, No. 79, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Anniversary of Well in Gregg County, No. 80 (with reel), 1966 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Lions Club, No. 81, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 82, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Permian Basin Petroleum Appreciation Day, No. 83, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 84, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Lions Club, No. 85, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Lions Club, No. 86, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - North Texas Oil and Gas Association, No. 87, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - San Antonio Manufactures Association, No. 88, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Byron Tunnell Appreciation Dinner, No. 89, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Rotary Club, No. 90, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Rotary Club, No. 91, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - West Texas Oil and Gas Association, No. 92, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Chamber of Commerce, No. 93, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Texas Aggregates Association, No. 94, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - National Transportation Week, No. 95, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Odessa Shrine Club Banquet, No. 96, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Tyler Desk and Derrick Club, No. 97, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 98, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Association of Oilwell Servicing Contractors, No. 99, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Longview Deak and Derrick Club, Bosses Night Banquet, No. 100, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - The Oil Industry- Its Economic Impact on Texas, Houston, TX, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 29)
  - Purchasing Agents Association of Houston, No. 101, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 30)
  - Anderson County Chamber of Commerce, No. 102, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 31)
  - American Petroleum Institute, No. 103, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 32)
  - Gus Mutscher, “Speaker’s Day,” No. 104, 1969 (Box 24, Folder 33)
  - Interior and Insular Affairs Committee, House of Representatives, No. 105, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Natural Gas Men of Houston, No. 106, 1970 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - The Import Policy and Its Effect on the Domestic Producing Economy, Dallas, TX, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Southwester Legal Foundation, No. 107, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers, No. 108, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Hawkins Central Treating Facilities, No. 109, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - North Texas Oil and Gas Association, No. 110, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Panhandle Producers/Royalty Owners Association, No. 111, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Houston Chronicle Special Oil Edition, No. 112, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Petroleum Electric Power Association, No. 114, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Texas Motor Transportation Association, No. 115, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - North Texas Gas Pipeline, No. 116, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Transportation Club of Dallas, No. 117, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - Texas Mid-Continent Oil and Gas Association, No. 118, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Houston Chronicle Special Oil Edition, No. 119, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - Petroleum Industry Engineers of A.I.M.E., No. 120, 1971 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - TIPRO, No. 121, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 17)
  - Comm. on Interior and Insular Affairs, No. 122, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 18)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers of A.I.M.E., No. 123, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 19)
  - Panhandle Producers/Royalty Owners Association, No. 124, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 20)
  - Longview Rotary Club, No. 125, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 21)
  - Offshore Louisiana Lease Sale Hearing, No. 126, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 22)
  - Oil Edition of San Angelo Standard-Times, No. 127, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 23)
  - Mike Halbouty Testimonial Dinner, No. 128, 1972 (Box 25, Folder 24)
  - Texas Outer Continental Shelf Sale, No. 129, 1973 (Box 25, Folder 25)
  - Packaging Corporation, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - “Politics-Act or React” Slides, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - “Politics-Act or React,” No. 130, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - President’s Meeting Slides, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - President’s Meeting, No. 131, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - “Act or React,” No. 132, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - 20 Minutes, No. 133, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Management, No. 134, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Speech for Training Program, No. 135, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Trying to Keep Up With Fifty State Governments, No. 136, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Management, No. 137, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Tyler Junior Chamber of Commerce Bosses Night and Past President Banquet, No. 138, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Ben Ramsey Appreciation Dinner, No. 139, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Texas Association of Business Meeting, No. 140, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Training 1st Governmental Affairs Dept, No. 141, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - “Governmental Affairs-The Flip Side,” No. 142, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - “Free Enterprise Fiesta Program,” No. 143, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Senator John Tower Annual Dinner, No. 144, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Impromptu, Delivered at Hearing, No. 145, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Governmental Affairs Workshop, No. 146, 1978 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - 66th Legislature, Speaker’s Day, No. 147, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Governmental Affairs Workshop, No. 148, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Johnson Retirement Party, No. 149, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Public Affairs Council Conference, No. 150, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Governmental Affairs Workshop, No. 151, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Texas Association of Business, No. 152, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Governmental Affairs Workshop, No. 153, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - TOC Political Education Seminar, No. 154, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Industrial Ecology’s Environmental Affairs Workshop, No. 155, 1981 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Tyler Jaycees Past Presidents/Bosses Night, No. 156, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 30)
  - Eulogy for P. Magum, No. 157, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 31)
  - PAC Meeting, No. 158, 1982 (Box 26, Folder 32)
  - Course in Middle Management, No. 159, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - American Petroleum Institute Lobbyist Seminars, No. 160 A-B, 1982 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Conoco External Affairs Group Slides, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Conoco Meeting, No. 160 C, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - PAC Meeting, No. 160 D, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Lone Star Lobsters, Gib Lewis Roast, No. 161, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - API Board Meeting, No. 162, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Remarks at P and M Luncheon, No. 163, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - API CPI Meeting, No. 164, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - API Property Tax Forum, No. 165, 1983 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Remarks to HL and P District Managers, No. 166, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Remarks to CPI, No. 167, 1984 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - “New Managers Seminar,” Tennecco, No. 168, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Eulogy for Ben Ramsey, No. 169, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - “New Managers Seminar,” Tenneco, No. 170, 1985 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - Corporate Communications Meetings, No. 171, 1986 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - Texas Women’s Political Caucus, 1987 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - Tribute to Bill Murray, University of Texas, No. 172, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Cedar Street Methodist Church 100 Years, No. 173, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Eulogy for Jim Slider, No. 174, 1990 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Introduction of Bullock, Baylor Distinguished Alumni, No. 175, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Gordon Bonfield’s Retirement TX, No. 176, 1991 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Jack Dillard Roast, No. 177, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Abington’s Retirement from TX MCOG, No. 178, undated (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Eulogy for Clint Barrow, No. 179, 1992 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Eulogy for Bob Johnson, No. 181, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Eulogy for Tom Creighton, No. 182, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Bob Bullock Texas Civil Justice League, No. 183, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Eulogy for Bob Bullock, No. 184, 1999 (Box 28, Folder 9)